In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company, the
market cap of the company is
5655 crores
and here you can see the chart of the company
and if we talk about the positive points in the company then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and the dividend payout of the company
and if we talk about the negative points then the
promoter's holding has
reduced by 7.83% in the last 3 years
and now let us also see the profit of the company
and the promoter's holding in share holding
is 48.024.07.2 At
this time the price of the company is
1152 rupees and the support in the share is 1120
and this share went up to 1650, make sure that the
fundamentals of the company are strong